Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran School of Art + Design records, circa 1908-2012 COR0009.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Student work, 1980-2019; Series 18
  - Student artwork, 1980-2019; Series 18 subseries 2
    - Student prints: Class of 1982, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 195, Segment 3)
    - Student prints: Class of 1983, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 195, Segment 4)
    - Student prints: Class of 1984, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 195, Segment 5)
    - Student prints: Class of 1985, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 195, Segment 6)
    - Student prints: Class of 1986, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 196, Segment 1)
    - Student prints: Class of 1987, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 196, Segment 2)
    - Student prints: Class of 1988, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 196, Segment 3)
    - Student prints: Class of 1989, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 197, Segment 1)
    - Student prints: Class of 1990, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 197, Segment 2)
    - Student prints: Class of 1991, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 198, Segment 1)
    - Student prints: Class of 1992, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 198, Segment 2)
    - Student prints: Class of 1993, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 198, Segment 3)
    - Student prints: Class of 1994, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 198, Segment 4)
    - Student prints: Class of 1995, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 199, Segment 1)
    - Student prints: Class of 1996, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 199, Segment 2)
    - Student prints: Class of 1997, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 199, Segment 3)
    - Student prints: Class of 1998, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 199, Segment 4)
    - Student prints: Class of 1999, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 199, Segment 5)
    - Student prints: Class of 2000, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 200, Segment 1)
    - Student prints: Class of 2001, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 200, Segment 2)
    - Student prints: Class of 2002, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 200, Segment 3)
    - Student prints: Class of 2003, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 201, Segment 1)
    - Student prints: Class of 2004, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 201, Segment 2)
    - Student prints: Class of 2005, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 201, Segment 3)
    - Student prints: Class of 2006, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 202, Segment 1)
    - Student prints: Class of 2007, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 202, Segment 2)
    - Student prints: Photojournalism seniors, 2007; Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 203)
    - Student prints: Class of 2008, Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 204)
    - Student prints: Photo magazine entry prints, circa 2000; Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 205)
    - Student prints: Photo magazine entry prints, circa 2000s; Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 206, Segment 1)
    - Student prints: unidentified, circa 2000; Series 18 subseries 2 (Box 206, Segment 2)
    - Corcoran Research Grant Project: Protest in Big Print, 2019 (Box 207)
      Woodblock prints inspired from Corcoran research group project exploring history, architecture, and/or community of DC and what these places or institutions reflect in our current social and political environment. Participants used the Washingtoniana collection as inspiration.
  - Summer Art & Writing Institute, 2001; Series 18 subseries 3
    Contains 12 booklets created in the Corcoran Summer Art & Writing Institute 2001.
    - Bombing by Luis Peralta, 2001; Series 18 subseries 3 (Box 293, Item 1)
    - Confessions by Mei-Wah Lee, 2001; Series 18 subseries 3 (Box 293, Item 2)
    - Crazy by Maira Rodriguez, 2001; Series 18 subseries 3 (Box 293, Item 3)
    - C*rsing by Ellen Estenia Mata, 2001; Series 18 subseries 3 (Box 293, Item 4)
    - Dreaming with eyes open by Jose Rivera, 2001; Series 18 subseries 3 (Box 293, Item 5)
    - Siblings by Andrea Roberson, 2001; Series 18 subseries 3 (Box 293, Item 6)
    - Some scars don't heal by Oscar Isac Moreno, 2001; Series 18 subseries 3 (Box 293, Item 7)
    - Survival by Adam Trejo, Series 18 subseries 3 (Box 293, Item 8)
    - Um... by Janali Thompson, 2001; Series 18 subseries 3 (Box 293, Item 9)
    - Untitled by Inocente Arevalo, 2001; Series 18 subseries 3 (Box 293, Item 10)
    - Wired by Monique Morgan, 2001; Series 18 subseries 3 (Box 293, Item 11)
    - Zone by Donnie Lee Joyner, Jr., 2001; Series 18 subseries 3 (Box 293, Item 12)